{
  "decks":[
    {
      "Title": "Spanish 2",
      "Description": "Sra. Mendoza's class",
      "cards":[
        {
          "Question": "One",
          "Answer": "Uno"
        },
        {
          "Question": "Two",
          "Answer": "Dos"
        },
        {
          "Question": "Three",
          "Answer": "Tres"
        },
        {
          "Question": "Four",
          "Answer": "Cuatro"
        }
        ]
    },
    {
      "Title": "U.S Capitals",
      "Description": "Memorize the capitals",
      "cards":[
        {
          "Question": "Alabama",
          "Answer": "Montgomery"
        },
        {
          "Question": "Alaska",
          "Answer": "Juneau"
        },
        {
          "Question": "Arizona",
          "Answer": "Phoenix"
        },
        {
          "Question": "Arkansas",
          "Answer": "Little Rock"
        },
        {
          "Question": "California",
          "Answer": "Sacramento"
        },
        {
          "Question": "Colorado",
          "Answer": "Denver"
        },
        {
          "Question": "Connecticut",
          "Answer": "Hartford"
        },
        {
          "Question": "Delaware",
          "Answer": "Dover"
        },
        {
          "Question": "Florida",
          "Answer": "Tallahassee"
        },
        {
          "Question": "Georgia",
          "Answer": "Atlanta"
        },
        {
          "Question": "Hawaii",
          "Answer": "Honolulu"
        },
        {
          "Question": "Idaho",
          "Answer": "Boise"
        },
        {
          "Question": "Illinois",
          "Answer": "Springfield"
        },
        {
          "Question": "Indiana",
          "Answer": "Indianapolis"
        },
        {
          "Question": "Iowa",
          "Answer": "Des Moines"
        },
        {
          "Question": "Kansas",
          "Answer": "Topeka"
        },
        {
          "Question": "Kentucky",
          "Answer": "Frankfort"
        },
        {
          "Question": "Louisiana",
          "Answer": "Baton Rouge"
        },
        {
          "Question": "Maine",
          "Answer": "Augusta"
        },
        {
          "Question": "Maryland",
          "Answer": "Annapolis"
        },
        {
          "Question": "Massachusetts",
          "Answer": "Boston"
        },
        {
          "Question": "Michigan",
          "Answer": "Lansing"
        },
        {
          "Question": "Minnesota",
          "Answer": "St. Paul"
        },
        {
          "Question": "Mississippi",
          "Answer": "Jackson"
        },
        {
          "Question": "Missouri",
          "Answer": "Jefferson City"
        }
        ]
    },
    {
      "Title": "Computer Science",
      "Description": "Web Design",
      "cards":[
        {
          "Question": "Computer Science Question 1",
          "Answer": "Computer Science Answer 1"
        },
        {
          "Question": "Computer Science Question 2",
          "Answer": "Computer Science Answer 2"
        },
        {
          "Question": "Computer Science Question 3",
          "Answer": "Computer Science Answer 3"
        },
        {
          "Question": "Computer Science Question 4",
          "Answer": "Computer Science Answer 4"
        },
        {
          "Question": "Computer Science Question 5",
          "Answer": "Computer Science Answer 5"
        }
        ]
    },
    {
      "Title": "Criminal Justice",
      "Description": "CJ1932",
      "cards":[
        {
          "Question": "Criminal Justice Question 1",
          "Answer": "Criminal Justice Answer 1"
        },
        {
          "Question": "Criminal Justice Question 2",
          "Answer": "Criminal Justice Answer 2"
        },
        {
          "Question": "Criminal Justice Question 3",
          "Answer": "Criminal Justice Answer 3"
        },
        {
          "Question": "Criminal Justice Question 4",
          "Answer": "Criminal Justice Answer 4"
        },
        {
          "Question": "Criminal Justice Question 5",
          "Answer": "Criminal Justice Answer 5"
        }
        ]
    }
    ]

}
